Daqi,
today's meal
is quite a bit over budget.
Ning'an County isn't far from here.
When will Jiaojiao come back?
She should be back soon.
Chief Su,
thank you for your care.
I'll take my leave now.
See you.
You'd better listen to your parents
and study hard.
Chief Escort Su
Do you want to control me like my father?
You're still in the play.
See you.
For escorts, come to Su's Agency.
Su's Escort Agency
The escort lives with the escort.
Well.
Cool.
Goodbye.
Boss, just let them go like this?
Yeah.
I think he's much better than those people.
How can I put a knife on his neck
and take him home?
Hehe, you can do it.
Didn't you just do it?
Do you want to be beaten?
We are escorts,
not bandits.
Let's go back to the escort agency.
Oh, right.
Gong Xi,
Remind me to get my money back from Matchmaker Pavilion.
Oh.
Okay.
Hello, sir.
Oh,
you're here.
Please come in.
Looks like
I'm in for tonight's Nebula Assembly.
You're so talented.
You deserve it.
Someone will take you to your seat later.
Thank you.
Sir,
bring all your signature dishes
and drinks.
Okay.
Please wait a moment.
OK.
You should drink the wine quickly.
When the Nebula Assembly starts later,
only the participants can stay in Huayue Tower.
Who has the final say
in the circle of literati in Yunjing?
Who?
The boss of Huayue Tower,
Zhang Xiyun.
Isn't she the boss of Cloud Bookstore?
In the entire Yunjing and even the Yun State,
as long as it's related to poetry and books,
it basically all belongs to her.
This woman is actually so impressive.
You must be from out of town, right?
She also organized the Nebula Assembly.
As long as you win the Nebula Assembly,
you can
become famous in the literary circle of the Yun State.
You are so insightful.
What exactly is the Nebula Assembly about?
Yicheng,
are you full?
How would I know?
No.
Check, please.
Eighty taels.
Are you kidding me?
This wine is the best in Yunjing City,
fifty taels a pot.
These dishes are also the best in Huayue Tower.
Do you two
do you want to run away from the bill?
It's okay.
I'll drink first.
Yicheng,
pay the bill.
Do you want to stay in the inn tonight?
Uh,
we have something to do later.
We'll choose a room when we come back.
Let's go.
You should come back as soon as possible.
Don't miss the Nebula Assembly.
Take care.
Wait.
Pack these up for me.
You can go now.
I won't marry you.
My Lord,
he's been waiting for you so long.
You just drove him away.
You're so rude.
I'm a bodyguard.
I don't need to be polite.
If you don't like it, just leave.
Dad.
Look at how she talks.
I don't want a husband like this.
Su Yuejiao.
I've inquired at the Matchmaker Pavilion.
Dabao meets
all your requirements.
If you want to stay at the escort agency,
Who else can marry into the Su family
in Yunjing City
except for Dabao?
If Dabao doesn't work out,
you won't be able to hold the seal.
You think Guo Yongshi is impolite.
Dabao should be polite, right?
Yeah, Dabao is very well-behaved.
He listens to me.
Hehe.
Can he escort goods?
He looks too weak.
He can.
He?
Humph.
Come here.
What?
Ah.
Come on.
Get away.
Sis,
She's been gone for six hours.
Young Master,
let's find a place to stay.
Fifty taels for a pot of wine.
Forget about lodging,
I can't even afford
the second round with my savings.
Wait here for me.
Okay.
Again.
Enjoy yourself.
Ah.
Nebula Assembly is about to start.
Come back tomorrow.
I'm Cheng Qi from Ning'an County.
I'm here to attend the Nebula Assembly.
Do you have any proof?
Proof?
I don't have any.
But
if you ask Shopkeeper Li,
and everything will be clear.
He's busy.
You can wait over there.
Hahaha.
Isn't this the second-in-command?
Young Master Shen.
The Nebula Assembly has been given to you.
Your business is booming.
Thanks to all of you.
Please come in.
This way.
Hey!
Why can he go in directly?
He doesn't have a pass either!
You bumpkin,
you don't even know me,
yet you dare to attend the Nebula Assembly?
Do you have a name on your face?
Do I need to know you to attend the assembly?
I won't argue with a lowlife like you.
This guy is here to stir up trouble.
Get him out of here.
Don't tarnish the reputation of the Assembly.
Get out of here!
Or I'll deal with you.
I'm not leaving.
Go ahead and report me.
I'll deal with someone like you.
Do I need to report it?
Stop!
Are you here to guard
or to make trouble?
Miss.
Miss Ying,
this guy said he came to attend the convention,
but it's already past the time for entry verification,
and he doesn't have a pass.
I think he's just a rascal.
Young Master Cheng,
don't be late next time.
Ah.
Young Master Cheng,
Please.
Oh, no.
Oh, my.
What should I do?
You can't beat me.
You can't beat me, right?
I told you.
You two are a good match.
Jiaojiao.
You should control your temper.
You can't
judge a book by its cover.
Pick a day
and get married.
Don't stop.
I'm not done yet.
Hehe, sister.
I won.
Can you marry me?
In that case,
why don't you set the date?
Five days later is a good day.
How about it?
Great!
Marry her!
Marry her! Marry her!
I think it's a good idea.
No.
Why not?
Because...
Su Yuejiao, tell me.
Why not?
I...
Because the boss has already...
Because the boss has already
got married.
What?
Hey,
do you know the guy
the guy sitting in the back?
Never seen him before.
Probably some poor scholar from nowhere.
Welcome to the Nebula Assembly.
Tonight is the preliminary round of the assembly.
I believe everyone is also aware
that the written exam content today
is actually very simple for everyone.
How come it's her?
All the selected works for today...
Has the Matchmaker Pavilion closed down?
have been compiled by the Cloud Bookstore
and placed on your tables.
You will perform your works
in order according to your seating.
If needed,
the musicians from the Huayue Tower will provide accompaniment.
I wonder how Miss Su is doing now.
She's coming out now.
Explain to me clearly.
Who did you marry?
Who is he?
How did you meet?
Did he
take advantage of you?
Brother,
do you want me to marry Zhen Dabao?
Of course not.
It's absolutely impossible.
So I have to find him right now.
Rather than marrying the man Su Lishi found,
I'd rather marry him.
Jiaojiao,
let's go back.
If Tang Xin finds out
I climbed over the wall...
Right.
But where is
Tang Xin?
Why are you so hesitant?
Chief Su,
there's a door.
Why did you climb over the wall?
Ah,
I'm relieved to see you.
Have you seen Tang Xin?
Tang Xin?
Why are you looking for her?
Well,
she knows I've been looking for a son-in-law.
She said there are many handsome
and talented young men at the Nebula Assembly.
So she asked me to come and have a try.
The Nebula Assembly
is a place for us to pick talents,
not for you to find a husband.
You're right.
But Miss Tang Xin asked me
to let you in.
You're really good friends.
Thank you.
If you need any help, just tell me.
I'll give you a discount.
No need to wait.
I have a task for you now.
Welcome back from Ning'an!
The show just started.
Good thing I got this for you.
Why do I need this?
I can't play music.
Just fake it till you make it.
Let me tell you,
there are plenty of handsome guys here.
Put on a show,
and you can stay longer.
Have you seen that guy we met before?
You finally got it!
How did you know he's here?
It's a long story.
To make it short,
I...
I accidentally married him.
Now I need his help.
You're married?
Keep your voice down!
What a lucky girl!
There he is.
Tell me what happened.
I have to take him back now,
or Su Lishi will force me to get married.
When will the Nebula Assembly end?
OK.
My dear.
One day without seeing you
is like a year.
Stop laughing.
Play the music.
I'll tell you later.
Hum.
I heard that you can't talk to other women
normally except for your sister.
Is that true?
It's done.
Chai.
Take it to the kitchen.
You two
are both geniuses.
Please play a piece of Butterfly in Love with Flowers.
♪Spring rain embraces willows.♪
Cliche.
♪Sipping wine,♪
♪only longing for beauty.♪
Slacking off here?
I must teach him a lesson for my parents.
It's none of my business.
♪Wine and flowers, flowers won't bloom.♪
♪Looking back, only the cold night moon.♪
Why are you laughing?
Sir,
hearing your tune,
I thought of an old friend.
It's quite amusing.
I thought you came for the Nebula Assembly,
but you're just here to listen to tunes.
You've got it wrong.
Your lyrics and tune,
while simple, are elegant.
I didn't mean to look down on them.
A nameless bumpkin like you,
what do you know about elegance?
The Nebula Assembly
is great
because it's inclusive.
As long as you have the passion
and the words in your heart,
even a village bumpkin can make a difference.
But,
with your talent,
we can't even fathom it.
Hahaha.
What are they laughing at?
Your husband is saying this young master
is vulgar and unbearable.
Oh.
Uh...
Thank you for bringing this interesting interlude.
Please return to your seats.
The meeting continues.
Wait.
What's your name?
Tell me.
I'm Cheng Qi,
from Ning'an.
Cheng Qi?
I'd like to see
what you can write.
Well,
Mr. Cheng...
In just a few days,
we can see a lifetime.
Seemingly unaware of sorrow's taste,
I ask where sorrow stems from.
All sorts of winds pass by the ear.
You call for a smile and it is achieved.
Yet I fear this reason is not sound.
What's the point of seeking fame and fortune?
Clinging to appearances in Zen only leads to bondage.
Originally, there is no distinction between you and me.
Detached from worldly affairs, far from the flow of dust.
If one must be drunk to find relief,
♪ But there's no wine in the cup. ♪
♪ How can I get drunk? ♪
♪ Who can hear the voice of flowers and the moon? ♪
♪ The wind is silent. ♪
♪ Spring is broken. ♪
♪ I wandered wildly in the deep alley. ♪
♪ Silks fluttering. ♪
♪ It's better to have red feathers falling from the sky. ♪
♪ They are gently swaying. ♪
♪ Red clouds falling. ♪
♪ Heroes' shadows fade, and people sigh. ♪
♪Only love remains♪
♪Between heaven and earth♪
♪Only loss♪
♪Is the most cherished♪
Bravo!
What a racket!
He should be disqualified from the Nebula Assembly!
Young Master, please behave yourself.
How dare you tell me to behave myself?
I'm just reciting from the booklet.
How could he change it?
He should be disqualified.
Please take him out.
Miss Zhang, it's him who broke the rules.
He didn't say the lines from the booklet.
Why should I be disqualified?
Because the Nebula Assembly
is
the rule.
Please.
Mr. Cheng.
The competition continues.
That's your boss?
Yes.
She looks petite,
but she has a strong aura.
Of course, she owns countless businesses.
Most of these young masters
are here for her.
Your husband is interesting.
He's not afraid of the powerful,
and he's reasonable and polite.
I agree with this marriage.
But can a man like him
be willing to marry into your family?
The contest is over.
The second round will be held at Huayue Tower.
The results will be posted
on the Public Opinion Column.
Mr. Cheng, you are so talented.
I admire you.
Mr. Cheng, you are so outstanding.
You're too kind.
I'm willing to concede defeat.
You flatter me.
He's a man of some importance,
as you're willing to defend him.
Mr. Cheng is a handsome man.
Even if he was unknown before,
he will rise rapidly in the world.
I've heard a lot about you.
Why don't we make friends?
You won't stay here tonight?
I'll go to my friend's house.
Thank you, innkeeper.
My lady specifically instructed that
if you come to Huayue Tower
before the second test,
all your expenses will be covered.
Please tell her
I appreciate her help.
This way.
If you don't hurry,
all the inns will be closed.
Don't panic.
I've found a place to stay.
Nebula Assembly paid the money.
No.
But
we got a man.
A man?
Chief Escort Su,
your brother just left.
Oh.
Next time you come here,
you can go through the front door.
Thank you, Shopkeeper Li.
You...
You tell me first.
Can you come back to the escort agency with me?
Didn't you say we should owe each other nothing?
Why do you need me so soon?
The situation is a bit complicated.
Besides, you still owe me a favor.
I need it right now.
Then tell me
what I can do for you.
I need you
as my
husband,
come home with me.
What?
Are you
going to run away from home?
Cut the crap.
Yes or no?
What if I say no?
Well,
that's impossible.
It must be possible.
But I have some conditions.
I'll agree to all of them.
Let's go now.
Hey.
They are all men,
most of them are skilled.
It seems that I have to overcome them by softness.
Have you remembered all the information?
Say it carefully later.
If you let slip the information,
don't expect to walk out of here today.
I'll handle this little situation.
He, he, he...
A Jiao.
It's delicious.
I want it.
You don't want it?
Why didn't you tell me
we were meeting elders today?
I didn't prepare anything.
It's so rude.
Sister.
You...
Mom.
Well,
I know grandpa likes the cakes of Huayue Tower.
I went there specially.
Grandpa likes cakes?
Did I say that?
Yes.
I remember everything about you
and your family.
Don't just stand there.
Introduce me to your family.
Take your hand off me.
You big dummy.
What are you doing?
Don't you see I'm eating candy?
Don't be mad.
Candy.
Later,
I'll give you more.
Humph.
What a blockhead.
This is my husband.
I've never heard Jiaojiao
mention you.
Do you have a marriage certificate?
And the betrothal gifts?
Tell me.
what are your intentions towards my sister?
Enough!
Young Master, where are you from?
When did you meet Jiaojiao?
I am Cheng Qi,
from Ning'an.
I'm the only child in my family.
My father is the county sheriff of Ning'an,
and my mother is a kind and gentle woman.
I met my lady by chance before.
I saw her act bravely,
and admired
her courage.
We met again in Ning'an,
and fell in love.
We got married right away,
without telling our parents.
We just couldn't help it.
Wait,
you married her?
Are you going to...
Even if I have to marry into her family,
I will
always be by her side.
How is it?
Is that enough?
You just say it.
You are good.
Gong Xi.
Master.
Check if dinner is ready.
Everyone must be hungry.
And
heat up the cake.
Yes, Grandpa.
Fa Cai,
prepare the room for the master.
Yes.
Go back to your room.
This liar
is not bad.
Have a seat.
Okay.
Do we all eat together?
Or what?
Hurry up.
Or the boss will eat all the meat.
Okay.
Here, my wife.
The boss actually
served someone.
We escorts are rough people.
We have to fight for food.
You have to learn to take care of yourself.
Otherwise, the food will be gone in a flash.
Uh.
Brother
I know you have many questions now.
But don't worry.
Because we haven't met your parents before,
we just followed our hearts and behaved ourselves,
and didn't dare to go beyond the rules.
Come on, my dear.
You agreed to let him marry into your family,
and you are so well-behaved.
You must be very open-minded.
Yes.
His father asked me to discipline him.
In this case,
you can live in the Escort Agency.
I'll invite your father here
to have a good talk.
Grandpa
Grandpa, have more.
Brother, you too.
Ten of them can't beat me.
They can't bully me.
I haven't had meat in three years.
Investigate Cheng Qi's background.
Do you think he's useful?
I'll know
after investigation.
Dad
Jiaojiao just left home for two days,
and she brought back a man,
saying she got married.
No marriage certificate, no betrothal gifts, no wedding night.
This marriage is invalid.
However,
since both of them
want to be the son-in-law of our escort agency,
and Jiaojiao has set the rules for marriage selection before.
Why not
let them have a competition?
You're so considerate.
I agree to compete with you.
Grandpa, no way.
It's not fair.
How is it unfair?
The Escort Agency doesn't support freeloaders.
That's what you said before.
What?
Is it that this Young Master Cheng
is not up to the task?
Just do as your uncle said.
Whoever loses,
leaves.
Are you crazy?
I can't even beat Zhen Dabao.
Don't worry.
I know what I'm doing.
As the son-in-law of the escort agency,
we should fight.
Whoever wins
can get A Jiao.
Isn't it the same as whoever pays more
gets the goods?
If you're afraid,
just admit defeat.
Why waste your breath?
Li Shi has a point.
To marry into the escort agency,
you need to know its business.
Young Master Cheng
also has a point.
Being an escort isn't just about brute force
or courage.
Choosing a husband
to choose a husband.
Dad.
So you mean
we should have
both martial and civil exams?
Tomorrow.
Show your real skills.
Compete on the field.